Crystal Prep students are super athletic
水晶预科学院的学生们运动超强
Super smart and super motivated
智慧卓绝 锐不可当
But there's one thing they aren't
但有一样东西 他们可没有
They aren't Wondercolts
他们不是闪电天马
We've fought magic more than once
我们已经不止一次与那神奇魔法战斗
And come out on top
而且最后都胜利了
Ah  oh
There's other schools But none can make those claims
其他的学校有很多 但是没有任何一所学校能做到这一点
Na na na na na
Together we are Canterlot
团结一心 我们是坎特拉高中
Come and cheer our name
快喊出我们的名字
Ah oh
This will be our year to win these games
今年比赛冠军一定是我们的
We'll always be Wondercolts forever
我们是战无不胜的坎特拉高中
And now our time has finally arrived
此时此刻 属于我们的光辉时刻已经降临
'Cause we believe in the magic of friendship
因为我们坚信友谊的魔力
And you know at the end of the day It is we who survive
你们会明白 最终 我们才是赢家
We're not the school we were before
我们的学校今非昔比
Before
今非昔比
Yeah we're different now
我们早已焕然一新
Ah oh
We overcame the obstacles we faced
面前的困难我们全都闯过来了
Overcame the obstacles we faced
全都闯过来了
We're Canterlot united United
坎特洛特团结一心  团结一心
We'll never bow
我们绝不屈服
Ah oh
Hey Hey
So get ready to see us in first place
准备好看我们登上冠军的宝座吧
We'll always be Wondercolts forever
我们永远都是坎特洛特高中的一员
Three! Two! One! Go!
三！二！一！冲啊！
And now our time has finally arrived Our time is now!
此时此刻 属于我们的光辉时刻已经降临 就是现在！
'Cause we believe in the magic of friendship
因为我们相信友谊的魔法
And you know at the end of the day it is we who survive
你们会明白 最终我们才是赢家
At the end of the day it is we who survive
最终我们才是赢家
Na na na na na na
Wondercolts united together
坎特洛特高中团结一致
Na na na na na na
Wondercolts united forever
坎特洛特高中永远齐心协力
We'll always be Wondercolts forever
我们永远都是坎特洛特高中的一员
Wondercolts united forever
坎特洛特高中永远齐心协力
And now our time has finally arrived
此时此刻 属于我们的光辉时刻已经降临
Wondercolts united forever
坎特洛特高中永远齐心协力
'Cause we believe in the magic of friendship
因为我们坚信友谊的魔力
Wondercolts united forever
坎特洛特高中永远齐心协力
And you know
你们会明白
At the end of the day
最终
It is we who survive
我们才是赢家
At the end of the day
最终
It is we who survive
我们才是赢家